namechk.com 2019-06-07

# Namechk | Username, Domain, and Trademark Search | Username Registration

Namechk.com is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Should you choose to provide your Email address or any other personal information on any of the forms found on our site, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with Namechk.com. This privacy policy is intended for all users of Namechk.com.

#### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION DOES NAMECHK COLLECT?

Namechk collects information from you when you register on Namechk or fill out a form.

Like most websites, Namechk uses cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'does Namechk use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

#### 2\. WHAT DOES NAMECHK USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information Namechk collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

#### 3\. HOW DOES NAMECHK PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

Namechk implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers.

#### 4\. DOES NAMECHK USE COOKIES?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

Namechk uses cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Namechk uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These third party ad service providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies in connection with advertisements offered through Namechk, including helping to operate ad networks. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. 

Namechk chooses to include information about Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie in its privacy policy. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site http://namechk.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to namechk.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

#### 5\. DOES NAMECHK DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

Namechk does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### 6\. THIRD PARTY SITES

Links to Products or Services: Occasionally, at our discretion, Namechk may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Ad Services and Providers: Namechk uses third party online behavioral advertising networks which include members of the Network Advertising Initiative. To learn more about their practices, and the choices they provide to you, including the option to opt out of behavioral advertising from advertising networks, please visit:

  * Digital Advertising Alliance – http://www.aboutads.info/choices 
  * NAI Participating Networks – http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating
  * Opt Out of Behavioral Advertising – http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

#### 7\. CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

Namechk is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### 8\. ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### 9\. TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Please also visit Namechk’s Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://namechk.com/terms-and-conditions

#### 10\. YOUR CONSENT

By using http://namechk.com, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### 11\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If Namechk decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 1/12/18.

#### 12\. CONTACTING NAMECHK

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://namechk.com

C/O Shore Light Group, LLC.  
9030 W Sahara Ave., Suite 395  
Las Vegas, NV 89117  
USA  
support@namechk.com
